ABOUT

I am a UX/UI designer experienced with User Experience Design, User Interface Design, and Visual Design. With the practical specializing in web design and app design, my enthusiasm, creativity and skills drive me to further explore the area of emotional design, human-computer Interaction. Lately, I am pursuing a Master's degree in Information Experience Design (IXD) at Pratt Institute.

Thesis: 92.0/100.0

GPA: 3.91/4.0

EDUCATION

Pratt Institute, New York, USA

Master of Science in Information Experience Design

Sept. 2019 - Present

• Pratt Institute Merit Scholarship.

National Kaohsiung Normal University, Taiwan

Master of Fine Arts in Visual Design

Sept. 2013 - Jun. 2016

• Academic Excellence Award: secured one gold medal and one silver medal for overall excellence.

Bachelor of Design in Visual Design

Sept. 2009 - Jun. 2013

- Academic Excellence Award: secured three gold medals and two silver medals for overall excellence.
- Awards: Ingenuity (Vision Get Wild Award, 2013), Pop-up Desire (HTC Packaging Awards, Silver Prize, 2011)

EXPERIENCE

Designer - Kronos Research Inc., Taipei

Feb. 2019 - May. 2019

- Devised Career web design including visual design, front-end developing and commercial photography.
- Directed visual design of Wallet App interfaces, prototypes, and created graphic materials of the final presentation.

UX Designer - Shopline Inc., Taipei

Feb. 2017 - Apr. 2018

- Designed Merchant App interfaces and conducted prototype interfaces in their business from anywhere.
- Prototyped new POS (Point of Sale) system and devised the user flow of the transaction process, product inventory and order management as the service of ecommerce shop and in-store business.
- Revamped Admin platform and standard storefront website with hi-fi prototypes on computers, tablets and mobiles, which is our major product increasing the profitability by 20% in five months.
- Compiled Design Guideline to be consistent with the current corporate identity system, which was used as the principle of product interface improvement.
- Designed customized storefront website and prototyped new screens across multiple devices, which increased the revenue over \$30,000 USD in ten months.

UI Desinger - Al Group Corp., Taipei

Oct. 2016 - Dec. 2016

- Devised front-end website design for the big opening campaign of JUT art museum.
- Created the interfaces of JUT App with the features including visitor reservation service, employee management and gym booking system for JUT Land Development Group.

UI Designer - Techgiant Inc., Taipei

Feb. 2016 - Aug. 2016

- Innovated visual identity of the project Robelf, the design is primarily used in the crowdfunding campaigns.
- Devised touchscreen interfaces and voice user interfaces with hi-fi prototypes for the tablet and mobile of Robelf mechanic products, which raised roughly \$150,000 USD funds in one year on Indiegogo.
- Organized and planned Robelf web design including the related graphic illustration and commercial photography, and prototyped the final solution for the website development.

SELECT SKILLS

Computer Graphics: Visual design, Branding, Photography, Video editing, 3d modeling

Design: User interface/ User experience design, Interactive prototypes, Web design (HTML/CSS/JavaScript)

Software: Sketch, Framer, Illustrator, Indesign, Lightroom, Photoshop, Premiere, After Effects, Autodesk Maya

Traditional Media: Pen/marker drawing, Pastel art, Watercolor, Acrylic painting, Oil painting